

### **PROFILE**

I am a software engineer and developer, experienced mainly on Microsoft technologies. Besides the professional experience, I have several research experiences on major branches of Computer Network (mainly software-defined networking).

I love open-source software, and would love to make my tools and utilities publicly available. I've been working on a stable web development methodology and technology, for both large-scale and regular size web applications. That one is closed source.

### **CONTACT**

PHONE: (+98) 918-713-4005

WEBSITE:

https://www.kiarash.pro

EMAIL:

kiarash.s@stu.razi.ac.ir hello@kiarash.pro

### **HOBBIES**

Hiking Cycling Book Reading Swim Listen to Music

# KIARASH SOLEIMANZADEH

CEO/Researcher/Web & Mobile Designer and Developer

### **EDUCATION**

### **Razi University**

2014 - 2018

Master of Information Technology (Multimedia Systems)

### **Malayer University**

2009 - 2014

Bachelor of Software Engineering

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Pouya Pardaz Karkia Company [CEO]

2014 - 2019

### Freelancer [Full Stack Developer]

2005 - Now

### **PORTFOLIO**

### Aja University of Medical Science Portal and Sub-Portals

Full Stack Developer (ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework Core, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, ...)

### Aja University of Medical Science Professors Comprehensive System

Full Stack Developer (ASP.NET MVC 5, Entity Framework 6, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, ...)

### **PUBLICATION**

## SD-WLB: An SDN-aided mechanism for web load balancing based on

### server statistics

2019 - Journal Paper

**Soleimanzadeh, K.**, Ahmadi, M., & Nassiri, M. (2019). **SD-WLB: An SDN-aided mechanism for web load balancing based on server statistics**. ETRI Journal. doi:10.4218/etrij.2018-0188

# RESEARCH INTERESTS Warehouse-Scale Computing (cloud, big data, bioinformatics) Electronic Commerce Software Engineering Computer Networks Database Systems Multimedia Systems Distributed Systems

SKILLS

- § C#/C/C++/Java/Matlab § Design Patterns § OO Design and Analysis § Software Project Management § DevOps § UML
- § CSS/HTML § TypeScript/JavaScript § C#/VB.NET § ASP.NET (Inc. ASP.NET Core) § Microsoft SQL Server § Angular
- § Microsoft IIS § Docker § Windows Server § Ubuntu/CentOS § MacOS § Git § WebPack/Gulp § MongoDB § Redis
- § Elasticsearch § Sass/Less § Entity Framework (Inc. EF Core) § .NET Framework (Inc. .NET Core)
- SignalR (Inc. Core SignalR) S Xamarin